[
  {
    "question": "age",
    "answer": "18_30"
  },
  {
    "question": "gender",
    "answer": "female"
  },
  {
    "question": "female_condition",
    "answer": "exclude"
  },
  {
    "question": "diet",
    "answer": "vegan,vegetarian"
  },
  {
    "question": "allergies",
    "answer": "soy,shellfish,eggs"
  },
  {
    "question": "med",
    "answer": "yes"
  },
  {
    "question": "med_daily",
    "answer": "benralizumab-subcutaneous,bentyl"
  },
  {
    "question": "med_occasionally",
    "answer": "guaifenesin-and-hydrocodone"
  },
  {
    "question": "drugs",
    "answer": "no"
  },
  {
    "question": "do_you_have_blood_tests_done_in_the_last_six_months",
    "answer": "no"
  },
  {
    "question": "do_you_have_your_dna_raw_data",
    "answer": "no"
  },
  {
    "question": "category",
    "answer": "exclude"
  }
]
